{"data":[{"question":"The young girl dreamed a dream that she was being carried away by monsters.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"dreamed","b":"a dream","c":"was being carried","d":"by","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- A dream-> the dream ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"It had been a long winter, but at last it was nearly across.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"had been","b":"but","c":"nearly","d":"across","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Across-> over","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"We can think of no reason about such strange behavior.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"think","b":"no","c":"about","d":"behavior","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- About-> for","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"Alan kept to try, although he didn't have much chance of success.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"to try","b":"although","c":"didn't have","d":"much","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- To try-> trying","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"When I moved into my new flat. I saw many furniture in it.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"When","b":"into","c":"many","d":"in it","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Many-> much","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"From 1785 to 1790, the capital of the U.S will be located in New York city.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"From","b":"to","c":"the","d":"will be located","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Will be located-> was located","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"The water in the Great Salt Lake is at less four times saltier than seawater.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The","b":"in","c":"at less","d":"saltier","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- At less-> at least","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"The Joneses have visited Hawaii and Alaska, and they assure me that they like Alaska the best.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"have visited","b":"and","c":"assure","d":"the best","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- The best-> the most","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"This refrigerator is very old to keep things at a proper temperature.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"very","b":"to keep","c":"at","d":"a","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Very-> too","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"He finally noticed that it was we, Diana and me, who always turned in the reports on time.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"finally","b":"we","c":"me","d":"turned","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Me-> us","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"}]}